buzzghana.com 2018-12-22

# Privacy Policy - BuzzGhana - Famous People, Celebrity Bios, Updates and Trendy News

Buzzghana.com takes your privacy seriously. We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our strong commitment to protecting your privacy. It outlines our information gathering, cookie policy, and privacy-related practices

Please review this Privacy Policy periodically as we may update it from time to time. Each time you visit the Site or provide us with information, you are, by doing so, accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy at that time. You agree that by using the website you are expressly and affirmatively consenting to our use and disclosure of the information that you provide, and consenting to receive emails if subscribed to us.

At Buzzghana.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by Buzzghana.com and how it is used.

**Information You Provide To Us**

We don’t set any first-party cookies, and we don’t track users in any personally identifiable way.

**Information You Provide to Us:**  We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. For instance, we may collect information you provide to us if you register on our website, respond to surveys, contact us through customer service or by other means, or participate in promotions that we may offer from time to time. Such information may include your name, email address or phone number. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features.

**Log Files**

Like most standard Web site servers, we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer to get information about the user.

We don’t set any first-party cookies to help deliver more targeted ads. However, we work with various reputable companies to help us analyze how our website is used and to optimize our Website to deliver the best possible experience. These companies may also include advertisers however, in such cases, we have no access or control over these cookies once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. If you wish to disable cookies, you can use the settings within your browser to control the cookies that are set on your computer or mobile device. However, please be aware that cookies are important to many aspects of our website – if you set your browser to reject cookies, you may not be able to enjoy all of the features on our platform. To find out how to see what cookies have been set and how to control, reject and delete cookies, please visit [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

**Links**

This Website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Site.

**Advertisers**

We may use different ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process and are collected by third-party advertising companies we use.

The number of adverts you see will not decrease if you disable these cookies but they may be less relevant to you. You can visit the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/) for more information about this practice and your possibility to opt-out.

**Third-Party Privacy Policies**

Here is a list of other third-party advertising vendors we work with along with a link to their privacy policy

**Google Analytics Privacy Notice**

Buzzghana.com uses Google Analytics to collect information about the use of our website. Google Analytics collects information from users such as how many people visit our website, how often they visit, what pages they visit, and what other websites they have been to before visiting our website. We use the information obtained from Google Analytics to analyze traffic and to improve our website. Google Analytics does not collect your name or other personally identifiable information. The service collects your IP address assigned to you on the date you visit our website. We do not combine the information collected using Google Analytics with any personally identifiable information. Google also uses specific identifiers and markers to help collect information about the use of our website. For more information on how Google collects and processes your data, visit [Google’s Privacy and Terms](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites). You can prevent Google Analytics from using your information by [opting-out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

**Children Under 13 Years of Age**

The Service is not directed to children. You must be 13 years and older to use the Service. As a result, we do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that information has been collected from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. We recommend that minors between the ages of 13 and 18 ask and receive their parents’ permission before using the Service or sending information about themselves or anyone else over the Internet.

**If you add content on this site:**

When you add any Content to this website: (a) you agree to grant to us a royalty-free, perpetual, non-exclusive worldwide right and license (including any necessary rights) to publish, reproduce, modify, use, display, adapt, distribute, archive, perform, promote, translate and create derivative works and compilations, in part or in whole. Such license will apply with respect to any form, media, technology known or later developed; (b) you represent and also warrant that you have all the necessary legal, moral, and other rights that may be needed to grant us with the license set forth in this Section (c) you also acknowledge and agree that we shall have all the necessary rights (but not obligation), using our sole discretion, to refuse to publish, to remove or block access to any Content you provide at any time and for any reason we may decide on with or without notice.

You agree to indemnify and hold us harmless, our subsidiaries, affiliates, related parties, officers, directors, employees, agents, independent contractors, advertisers, partners, and co-branders from any claim or demand, including reasonable attorney’s fees, that may be made by any third party, that is due to or arising out of your conduct or connection with this website or service, your provision of Content, your violation of this Terms of Use or any other violation of the rights of another person or party.

**Legal Disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on any of our sites.

**Notification of Changes**

Whenever we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy page, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

**Contact Information**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by filling out our contact form when you [click on this link](http://buzzghana.com/contact/) or write us at:

Alexander Moore Partners Ltd

Suite D3, Garden Avenue,

GRA,

Enugu State

Nigeria
